<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Business plan | XinyingCai's website</title><link>https://cecicxy.github.io/tag/business-plan/</link><atom:link href="https://cecicxy.github.io/tag/business-plan/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><description>Business plan</description><generator>Wowchemy (https://wowchemy.com)</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><image><url>https://cecicxy.github.io/media/icon_hub952b5b5292cfc503b29e8beb52f4289_3262_512x512_fill_lanczos_center_3.png</url><title>Business plan</title><link>https://cecicxy.github.io/tag/business-plan/</link></image><item><title>Hangzhou Olympic Sports Center Smart Energy Platform</title><link>https://cecicxy.github.io/project/hangzhouo/</link><pubDate>Fri, 20 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cecicxy.github.io/project/hangzhouo/</guid><description>&lt;p>I investigated and gained knowledge about the Internet of Things (IoT) infrastructure used in the construction of smart energy systems. This involved studying various components such as the external system, data integration, database management, platform back-end, and platform front-end.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>One of the key aspects I focused on was the external system, which refers to the integration of the smart energy system with external devices or systems. This could include sensors, meters, or other IoT devices that collect data related to energy consumption, such as cooling, heating, and electricity usage. Understanding how these external systems interact with the smart energy system was crucial for developing effective energy management strategies.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Data integration played a vital role in the construction of smart energy systems. It involved aggregating and consolidating data from different sources, including the external devices mentioned earlier. This process required developing protocols and interfaces to ensure seamless communication between the various components of the system. By integrating data effectively, it became possible to gain a comprehensive view of energy consumption patterns and identify potential areas for optimization.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Managing the vast amount of data generated by smart energy systems required a robust database infrastructure. I studied the design and implementation of databases capable of handling high volumes of data efficiently. This involved selecting appropriate database technologies, optimizing data storage and retrieval processes, and ensuring data integrity and security.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The platform back-end formed the core of the smart energy system, responsible for processing and analyzing the collected data. I delved into techniques such as data preprocessing, work condition analysis, and correlation analysis to derive valuable insights from the energy consumption data. Load prediction was another important aspect I explored, as it allowed for better resource planning and optimization of energy usage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The platform front-end served as the user interface for interacting with the smart energy system. This involved creating visualizations and dashboards that presented energy consumption data in a clear and understandable manner. By providing users with real-time information and control options, the front-end interface empowered them to make informed decisions regarding energy usage.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>my investigation into the IoT construction of smart energy systems encompassed various aspects, including the external system, data integration, database management, platform back-end, and platform front-end. By understanding the intricacies of each component, I gained insights into how these systems operate and contribute to efficient energy management. This knowledge is crucial for developing sustainable and intelligent solutions to address the challenges of energy consumption in today&amp;rsquo;s world.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Policy recommendation system</title><link>https://cecicxy.github.io/project/policyrecommend/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://cecicxy.github.io/project/policyrecommend/</guid><description>&lt;p>The system uses enterprise users&amp;rsquo; basic information, including location, sector, business scope, revenue, and past search records, to provide timely and accurate recommendations for relevant policies. This ensures that enterprises can access useful information that is tailored to their specific needs.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The system&amp;rsquo;s recommendation algorithm is inspired by the patent titled &amp;ldquo;Federal Bayesian Personalized Ranking Recommendation Method and System based on Multi-Krum.&amp;rdquo; This patent introduces a method that combines Bayesian inference with personalized ranking to enhance the accuracy and effectiveness of recommendations. By leveraging the Multi-Krum algorithm, the system further improves the reliability and robustness of the recommendations.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>When enterprise users provide their basic information, such as their location, sector, and business scope, the system analyzes these details to understand their specific context. By considering factors such as regional regulations, industry-specific policies, and the scope of their operations, the system can identify the most relevant policies for each enterprise.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Additionally, the system takes into account the revenue information of enterprise users. This helps in recommending policies that align with the financial capabilities and resources of each enterprise. By tailoring the recommendations to the financial context of the enterprise, the system ensures that the policies suggested are realistic and feasible.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The system also utilizes past search records of enterprise users to enhance the accuracy of its recommendations. By analyzing the historical preferences and interests of each user, the system gains insights into their specific areas of focus. This allows the system to provide targeted recommendations that align with the enterprise&amp;rsquo;s past interests and search patterns. By leveraging this personalized approach, the system increases the likelihood that the recommended policies will be relevant and valuable to the enterprise.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>Overall, the system&amp;rsquo;s goal is to provide enterprise users with useful and timely information about relevant policies. By considering their basic information, revenue, and past search records, the system can tailor its recommendations to the specific needs and context of each enterprise. The algorithm, inspired by the patent on Federal Bayesian Personalized Ranking Recommendation Method and System based on Multi-Krum, ensures that the recommendations are accurate, reliable, and robust. With this system in place, enterprises can make informed decisions and stay updated on policies that are relevant to their operations.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>